

CONTACT

(+62)813 8252 2328

david.santana.1112@gmail.com

Jalan Delima Utara II no.28
Waru, Sidoarjo

https://github.com/dapidmini

https://bit.ly/portfolio-davidsantana-v1



MAIN SKILLS

- Front End Coding (JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJS)
- Back End Coding (PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter)
- Database Design and Programming (MySQL)
- Image and Video Editing
- Microsoft Office
- · Active and Passive English

OTHER SKILLS

- Strong Communication Skills
- Problem Solving
- · Attention to detail
- Fast arithmetic
- · Strong logical understanding

Fullstack Web and Software Engineer

David Santana

I am a professional web developer with more than 10 years of experience in developing desktop and web based software applications using front-end and back-end programming with various frameworks. I am always eager to learn and adopt new technologies to expand my technical knowledge. I'm committed to writing clean, efficient, and maintainable code that adheres to the industry's best practices to produce the best results.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - 2024 Web Developer (PT. Gotravelly Media Indonesia)

- Developing and maintaining the Gotravelly website for users to post culinary and travel destinations.
- Actively involved in research and applying the latest technologies (NodeJS, Laravel 10, Al) to deliver the best user experience.
- Gain deeper and better understanding about Git Version Control.

2016 - 2017 Web Engineer (Teh Villa)

- Design, develop, and maintain web-based inter-department application to increase the efficiency in the company.
- Provide better reporting system to support the management.

2015 - 2016 Software Developer (PT. Global Business Solution)

- Develop and maintain software applications based on clients' needs.
- Learn to work with bigger team on multiple projects.
- Learn how to handle clients, e.g. gathering data and specifications.

2012 - 2014 Software Engineer (PT. Surya Timur Sakti Jatim)

- Design, develop and maintain desktop-based applications for multiple departments in the company.
- Provide better support system for the related departments, i.e. HR and Accounting.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

- Providing Indonesian to English Video Translation and Subtitling Services.
- Editing and Designing social media posts for non-profit organization.
- Teaching martial art (Aikido) to various people of various age groups for more than 10 years.

EDUCATION

2006 - 2012

Sekolah Tinggi Teknik Surabaya (STTS)

or

Institut Sains dan Teknologi Terpadu Surabaya (iSTTS)

Bachelor of Computer Science, Software Engineering major